# MATTEO GREGORICCHIO

Date of Birth 21/10/1992 Address corso Casale 210, Torino - 10132 Phone +39 338 661 3822 Email matteo.gregoricchio@mail.com matteo.gregoricchio@libero.it Personal Site www.matteogregoricchio.com Linkedin https://it.linkedin.com/in/matteogregoricchio



Upwork

http://www.upwork.com/o/profiles/u sers/ ~01ca9d34312f7fa73d/

I'm an Art History Graduate. During my studies I worked as a freelancer translator on the platform Upwork. Currently I'm studying the fundamental technologies (HTML, CSS, Javascript and Jquery, Ruby on Rails) to become a **full-stack developer**.

My best traits & skills are synthesis, precision and work organization. I'm an order passionate, I'm independent and I'm really resolute: if I have a task, I don't stop until I've completed it! You can find proof on my Upwork profile, where you'll see how I've always completed on time my contracts with max rating.

My main interests are contemporary art (with a focus on Latin America production), videogames, literature, the IT field (especially web programming) and the World Wide Web. Lastly, I'm a football fan!

### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Web Support at DeltaTre

06/2018 - current

Monitoring of uefa.com and fifa.com sites during live events of those two associations. Use of monitoring equipment and tools developed by DeltaTre. I also work as I^ level technical support (in english) for operators/editors working during live events. Intermittent job.

### Freelance Translator at Techpump S.L.

05/2015 - current

Translation projects eng-ita, online cultural contents.

# Internship at Polo Museale del Piemonte, Torino (TO)

11/2016 - 12/2016

Internship for Master's Degree. Employee at Education and Services Office. 150 hours.

### Freelance Translator at WebInterpret

02/2015 - 11/2015

Translation/adaptation to italian of englistings for e-commerce platforms.

# Traineeship at Technical Office, Moruzzo (UD)

03/2014 - 05/2014

Archive catalogation at Technical Office, Moruzzo (UD). Stage part of Bachelor's Degree program.250 hours.

### **EDUCATION**

### Master's Degree, Art History

2015 - 2017, Università degli Studi di Torino [Final Grade: 110 e Lode/110]

Dissertation: Il conceptualismo ideológico nell'Argentina degli anni '70: analisi dell'operato del Grupo CAYC; supervisors: José Luis de la Nuez Santana, Franca Varallo; topics: latinamerican contemporary art, contemporary argentine art ('60-'70 of the 20th century).

# **Bachelor's Degree, Conservation of Cultural Assets**

2011 - 2015, Università degli Studi di Udine [Final Grade: 108/110] Dissertation: *Julio Castellanos e i Contemporáneos;* supervisor: Mario Sartor; topics: latinamerican contemporary art, contemporary mexican art ('20-'40 of the 20th century).

### Secondary School Diploma

2006 – 2011, I.S.I.S. Vincenzo Manzini, San Daniele del Friuli (UD)

### LANGUAGE COMPETENCE

► Italian: Mother Tongue

English: Professional KnowledgeSpanish: Professional Knowledge

### IT COMPETENCE

- **ECDL Certificate** n. IT 1049910, released from AICA on 25/01/2007.
- Advanced Knowledge of Windows and Apple Systems.
- **Advanced** Knowledge of Microsoft **Office** and **LibreOffice** suites.
- **Advanced** Knowledge of **web surfing** and **web searching** and **e-mail systems**.
- Sood Knowledge of HTML & CSS.
- Basic Knowledge of Javascript & jQuery.

#### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

# **COURSES**

### **> Full-Stack Developer Career on Lacerba.io**

01/2018 - today

on course 6/7 (jQuery). The career focuses on those programming languages:

1-4. HTML & CSS 5-6. Javascript & jQuery 7. Ruby on Rails.

[List and courses syllabus is on: http://lacerba.io/p/full-stack]

In compliance with the Italian legislative Decree no. 196 dated 30/06/2003, I hereby authorize you to use and process my personal details contained in this document.

Turin, 09/2018